https://ca.privacy.cbs/

Search
California Consumer Protection Act (“CCPA”)
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides consumers who are residents of the State of California with specific rights related to their personal information, subject to certain exceptions. It also requires us to disclose the information we collect, the purposes for which we collect it, and what we share and disclose.
The Personal Information We Collect and Why
You have the right to know what personal information we collect and why. The information we collect and the purposes for which we use it are described in this Privacy Policy.
The Personal Information We Share or Disclose
You have the right to know what personal information we disclose or share with third parties. The personal information we share is described in this Privacy Policy.
Right to Know
You have the right to ask us what personal information we have collected from you over the past 12 months. You may make such requests up to twice a year.
Right to Delete
You have the right to ask us to delete your personal information. In certain circumstances the law may not require or permit us to delete certain personal information, but if we cannot honor a deletion request, we will tell you.
Right to Opt-Out (“Do Not Sell”)
You have the right to tell us not to disclose or transfer your personal information to a third party in exchange for something of value. The CCPA refers to this as your right to say “Do Not Sell” my personal information. If you opt out of disclosure or transfer of your personal information, you may later opt-in again to having your personal information move more freely.
13-15 Year Olds
We automatically opt-out consumers whom we actually know are at least 13 and less than 16 years old. In the language of the CCPA, we “do not sell” their personal information unless they opt-in.
Financial Incentives
We do not offer any financial incentives for consumers to take any action or make any choices in using our services.
Non-Discrimination
We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of the rights described in this Privacy Policy. Specifically, we will not deny you goods or services or charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits, or by imposing penalties.
Exercising Your Rights
Right to Know and Right to Delete
You may ask us for the personal information we have about you, or ask us to delete your personal information, by accessing our CCPA Rights Management Tools available at privacy.cbs/managemyrights or by calling 1(888)-841-3343. When you make a request online, we will verify your identity by sending you an email and asking you to respond. When you call the toll-free number, you must leave a name, address, and email address we can use to contact you.
If you ask what personal information we have received from you, and we cannot verify your identity, or if providing the information you have requested creates a security risk, we will give you a general description of the type of personal information we have about you.
If you ask us to delete your personal information, and we can’t verify your identity and confirm that you made the request, we will not be able to honor it. Generally, though, if we can confirm your identity and your request, we will delete, de-identify, or aggregate your personal information so it can no longer be associated with you. There are some reasons that the law may require or permit us to keep your personal information, however.
Opt-Out (Do Not Sell)
If you do not want us to disclose or transfer your personal information to a third party in exchange for something valuable, you may opt out by visiting ca.privacy.cbs/donotsell or calling 1(888)-841-3343. When you call our toll free number, you will need to leave a name, address, and email address that we can use to contact you.
Authorized Agents
If you are an authorized agent, you must submit your request at https://privacy.cbs/managemyrights. We will contact you with further instructions to process your request in accordance with the CCPA requirements. In general, you will need to provide proof that you are registered with the Attorney General, as required by law, and proof you have written authority to act for the consumer. You shall also provide the email address of the consumer you are representing so we can verify their identity, or provide documentation that you have power of attorney for the consumer pursuant to Probate Code sections 4000-4465. We will not be able to honor requests without sufficient documentation that you are authorized to represent the consumer or that you are registered with the Attorney General.
Requests made on behalf of a “Household”
If you would like to request personal information about your household, you must submit your request at http://privacy.cbs/managemyrights. We will contact you with further instructions to process your request.  We will need to verify the members of the household, and in some cases, if a request raises security concerns for any household member, we may not be able to honor the request
California “Shine the Light” Law and California “Eraser” Law
Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which we have disclosed certain information during the preceding year for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes.
If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a user of the website where this policy is posted, you may request removal of content or information you have publicly posted. Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete removal from the Internet of the content or information you posted, and there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal.
For all requests under the “Shine the Light” Law, please submit your request at http://privacy.cbs/managemyrights. We will accept requests to exercise these rights only through this form with the proper subject line and complete and accurate information.
Contacting Us
You may contact us with questions about Your California Rights or our Privacy Policy and practices here or
CBS Interactive Inc.
Information for Visitors from the European Union (EU)
©2020 ViacomCBS - All rights reserved.
